You're all right. Let's go good. You're here. I was hoping that you would be
This is what happens when you put your trust in humans out of the way vampire
Why are they fighting Gurren?
He's strong. What's the matter? You put up a much better fight in Shinjuku. He's like a different person
That's enough let's begin
Drink the blood of a human a demon and a progenitor
Hey, Gurren. What's wrong? Why are you fighting us?
What is all this?
The Seraph of the End
It's coming. See it? Our punishment for breaking their taboos. It's heaven's judgment
We must seize control of that power
That light. What is it?
What is it?
It's... an angel
The Seraph of the End
I... I... I...
You humans are Blasphemers. You've brought Broncos out.
the Seraph of the End
And...
and bo abstain
the Seraph of the End
Well, well. That's quite impressive. Let's watch.
Hurry, capture the Angel.
No, you monsters. That's my sister. What have you done to her?
Enough, kid. Time to stand down.
Have you gone insane?
Now, you! Attack!
What's wrong? Don't tell me you've gone soft on me.
This isn't right, Gurren. This isn't you. Did they brainwash you or something?
You trained us. You taught us to never turn our backs on our comrades.
Stop smiling and say something already. You know who we are.
Please. We're still your family, Gurren.
You're crying?
You know!
Is he okay?
Me and I...
There it is.
Blowing the fifth trumpet summoned the demon of destruction, Abaddon.
Our enchantments and curses worked. We've succeeded in controlling the Seraph of the End.
Ahoye, you know what to do next.
Sir!
Everyone, we need to retreat.
Come on, let's go, Kamizuki.
Get off of me! I'm not leaving Mino behind!
No, wait! Don't do it!
Go ahead and escape.
This battle is personal now.
Kamizuki!
This is the end of it all.
There's no future for any of us now.
Move!
Where is he?
You. Good, you're awake.
We're gonna find a safe place.
Somewhere they won't be able to reach.
I have to help Gorin.
He was crying earlier.
It's still him.
Are you kidding me? Forget about Gorin.
And Shinoa?
Where are my comrades?
I think they're staying behind to fight.
We have to go back and help.
I can't leave them to die.
Amika, they're my family.
No, I'm your only family, you.
Listen to me!
There's Gorin, and Shinoa,
Yorichi, Kimizuki, Mitsuba, and you.
You're all people I have to protect.
Understand?
You're hurt.
Oh, crap.
Quick, you have to drink my blood.
No, that won't help me.
There's something about this demon that affects my healing.
Then what can I do?
You can save yourself.
Look at that thing.
There's no way we can take it down.
Your family is in danger.
Go save them.
Shut up.
It's not like I can leave you here to die.
Not now.
I just got you back, Mika.
I won't lose you again.
Just go, you idiot.
Hurry.
Or else you'll lose your whole family again.
All I need to do is kill that big monster, right?
That'll save everyone, including you.
You've always had the worst ideas.
Use your damn head for once.
That thing's huge.
No one can kill it.
Maybe not.
But I'll sure as hell try.
Okay.
You don't.
You really want to save them that badly?
Yep.
I'm afraid my power won't be enough.
I know.
Then you're really here to betray me, huh?
You've come back for the golden trumpet.
I told you it was bad news.
It's the only way.
If you use that thing, you'll lose your humanity.
You'll become something else.
Your family might not recognize you anymore.
I don't care.
Anything to keep them all safe.
Queen Cruel.
This is bad.
They've stopped attacking us.
What's going on?
Maybe that thing's to blame.
Probably a safe bet.
It's you.
You.
My sister.
Please.
You've got to help her.
What is that tower of flame?
Kurato, sir.
We're getting new Seraph of the End readings.
They're coming from the fire.
Well, what does that mean?
I'm not sure.
But, sir, if we fail to investigate it...
...then we might watch the world end again, right?
This must be heaven's wrath.
But, even if God himself is our enemy...
...humankind will defeat him here.
Aoi.
Sir.
Destroy it.
All units move in.
Strike hard.
Destroy that Seraph.
You too, Abaddon.
Abaddon!
You too, Abaddon!
The time has come to end this world.
I'll judge every human who's broken our taboos
and turned them into pillars of salt.
What the fuck?
Get out of the way!
We don't have time!
Fire!
That's the second trumpet!
Lieutenant Shinro Furuto!
It's the King of Salt!
I don't care!
Kill him!
Fully!
No!
stop
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
Now.
You.
It's over.
The lust for power that drives you humans ends today.
All before me will become pillars of salt.
All units. Target Yuichiro Hyakuya. Capture him, sir!
Whoa, interesting. You've gone crazy. Welcome to the club.
Humans aren't worthy of this world.
You're losing sight of your goals, Yu. I said I'd help you get your vengeance.
Unfortunately, right now, there's only one way for me to do that.
I have to take complete control.
Not good. We have to get him.
We should go too, Queen Kru.
Are you healed enough?
I'll be fine.
Good. Don't let the humans get a hold of him. You've seen what they'll do.
Right.
I'm not done yet.
Really? Because I meant to differ.
My queen, you've panicked and left your beautiful neck wide open.
Queen Kru!
Forget me!
Mika, go!
Now!
That's better.
Wow, Ferret.
You've captured the queen. Impressive.
I guess I was a good distraction.
You sound as though you doubted me.
I'm curious.
Where does that leave us, now that our leader has been taken out of the equation?
Listen, vampire brethren.
We've just discovered that Krul Tepesh is guilty of high treason against our kind.
She was involved in the human serif of the end experiment that could have completely destroyed us.
Therefore, as the seventh progenitor, I, Ferret Bathory, am assuming control.
Oh, so you're still alive. I'm glad you managed to make it out of this okay.
Narumi, I'm short on time. Hurry up and give him to me.
I'm sorry, Lieutenant Colonel.
But I can't follow your orders. Not after what you've done.
What are you doing?
Take him!
Step aside.
Don't let them escape!
Lieutenant General, they're coming.
Always more vampires. Kill them!
What the hell's going on, Gurren?
Don't laugh at me. Explain yourself!
You can't be mad at me, Shinya.
I'm just doing what we dreamed about way back when we were kids.
What are you talking about?
I'm changing the whole world. It's gonna be a different place.
One where second tier people like you and me can actually move up.
Have you lost your mind?
You killed our own men!
Your betrayal destroyed us! Our comrades are dead!
No.
You've been possessed.
Hey, listen to me. You're still in there somewhere!
Shirawa, wait! What about Kamizuki's sister? She's still back there!
It's okay.
Are you sure?
Hand over Yuichiro Hyakuya immediately. That's an order.
We no longer take orders from you. As of now, my team's withdrawn from the demon army.
More will follow them. Hurry!
Move it as fast as you can!
I'm not losing any more comrades today.
Kuruto, sir. Everything's in order. We're ready to advance.
Excellent. Let's not waste any more time.
Now this is where things get really interesting.
We're ready to go.
Is that the last of it?
Yeah.
Where are those two?
They'll be out in just a minute.
We're taking your time.
You're always in a rush, that's all.
You. Where's your demon?
Oh.
Sleeping.
Don't worry about it.
Let's go.
We'll rescue Kamizuki's sister and the idiot, Gurin, too. We'll get him back to his old self.
You're sure the lieutenant colonel is really ensanguing them?
Yes. The intel I got was solid.
Jeez. We ran away and now we have to go all the way back? What a pain.
Just don't do anything dumb like grow wings and try to kill us all when we get there.
Why would you say something like that, Mika? Besides, I saved the day.
You should bring back the demon horns. It was a good look for you.
It's gonna be a long trip.
You will be fine. I mean, there's no way things could get any worse than they were, right?
Did you hear that? It's all good.
It's starting to rain.